DESMOND OFORI

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



1 054-129-8861

oforidesmond@rocketmail.com

633 First Okle Road, Accra

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional software-developer with three years of experience in web and mobile application design and currently employed as a Software Development Officer at infoGate.Net. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

SKILLS

- NodeJs /JavaScript
- ReactJS / React Native
- Tailwind / Bootstrap
- Express / SQL
- Problem-Solving
- Strong Communication Skills
- Project Management Tools
- UI / UX
- Web Design
- Troubleshooting and Repair

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

ACCRA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

2021 - PRESENT

CCNA CERTIFICATIONS

GHANA-INDIA KOFI ANNAN CENTRE 2014 - 2015

CERTIFICATE IN HARDWARE

PROMAX COMPUTER TRAINING **2014**

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

NUNGUA SNR. HIGH SCHOOL 2011 - 2014

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT OFFICER

INFOGATE.NET LIMITED

APRIL 2023 - PRESENT

- Crafting robust and scalable web and mobile applications.
- Manage the company servers and data.
- · Providing technical support.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER (INTERN)

WHITSUN SYSTEMS LIMITED

JUNE 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2022

- Web Application design
- Built the logic for a data logging application that scaled.
- Redesigned and upgraded web-applications for the company.

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN

FREELANCE

2014 - PRESENT

- Assembled desktop computers for clients
- Actively trobleshoot and repair computers for clients
- Engaged in projects for the administering of computers for educational institutions